<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfHouse xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <House>
    <Name>Church</Name>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Name>Adoloscent kids are protestings at church door</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Join the kids in protest, not knowing what they are protesting about</Name>
            <News>Rabble rousers find a new leader and get more organised as ever. Nobody is safe!</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Use your political power to disperse the crowd</Name>
            <News>14 dead as the Mayor releases nerve gas to disperse a peaceful protest.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Release the priests</Name>
            <News>Priest found that nobody knew was missing.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>The Raelian Movement come to you to offer their new trendy religion. For a fee.</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>You are a busy man and let your intern handle it.</Name>
            <News>10 things that interns are perfect for, you wouldnt believe number 7!</News>
            <Doom>-3</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>You welcome the new religion and rise taxes to pay for the fee.</Name>
            <News>New religion takes hold in the village, human sacrifice rate higher than ever!</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>You release the hounds</Name>
            <News>Children playing pokemon GO found mauled in the alley, Mayor looking for the culprit.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>Someone has stolen the cross</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Search every house in the village for the cross.</Name>
            <News>Community more united than ever as the search for the cross continues.</News>
            <Doom>-2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Give the church a new cross.</Name>
            <News>Church furious as the new cross turned out to be made out of cheese.</News>
            <Doom>4</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Tell them you took the cross.</Name>
            <News>Kleptomania gone wrong! Find out more on page 8.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>A marriage has been canceled because the bride is missing</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Become the bride</Name>
            <News>Same sex marriage a thing?? Critics say maybe.</News>
            <Doom>4</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Offer your wife as a bride</Name>
            <News>God is angry as polygamy becomes more popular than ever!</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Blame the priest for losing the bride.</Name>
            <News>The serial bride snatcher caught. Bride population increasing.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
    </Questions>
  </House>
  <House>
    <Name>Tavern</Name>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Name>Beer taps are empty!!</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Fill them with holy water</Name>
            <News>Spontanious combustion spreads like a wildfire while the quality of life increases.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Fill them with unholy water</Name>
            <News>Satanic metal more popular than ever, cause yet to be found.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Fill them regular water</Name>
            <News>The hangover epidemic cured! Turns out more booze was not the answer after all.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>A random RPG party appears and asks if you have a quest</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Tell them that there are rats in the cellar that need to be slain.</Name>
            <News>PANIC! Group of roleplayers found dead in a cellar.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Tell them that a cult has built their headquarters in the city center.</Name>
            <News>Nuns slaughterd as a group of roleplayers mistake the monestary for the cult house.</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Chase the roleplayers away.</Name>
            <News>New policy against role playing announced, effective immediately!</News>
            <Doom>-2</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>Intern wants you to try his experimental beer</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Try it</Name>
            <News>Man poisoned for drinking fermented leftovers.</News>
            <Doom>4</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Take it and give it to your wife.</Name>
            <News>Mayor accused for poisoning the wife!</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Politely refuse</Name>
            <News>People feel uneasy as nothing peculiar has happened.</News>
            <Doom>0</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>The pub is burning!</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Run to the exit, screaming.</Name>
            <News>Freak birthday accident. 12 dead, mayor the only survivor.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Doze the fire with your drink.</Name>
            <News>Man tries to extinguish fire with ethanol, makes things worse.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Relax and enjoy the warmth while everyone in the pub tries to extinguish the fire.</Name>
            <News>10 facts about why a burning bar is not a sauna. Find out more on page 12.</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>The barman has passed out.</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Take a free drink.</Name>
            <News>Religous man running through the streets naked, gets ignored by everybody.</News>
            <Doom>0</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Throw a pucket of water at him.</Name>
            <News>Water Bucket murderer strikes again!</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Go to sleep besides him.</Name>
            <News />
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
    </Questions>
  </House>
  <House>
    <Name>Market</Name>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Name>The village joker is making an improv show</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Boo him off the stage</Name>
            <News>Have improv shows gone too far? God says, yes!</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Join the jokers show</Name>
            <News>Naked man interrups a improv show, the crowd was pleased.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Get inspired and create your own improv show</Name>
            <News>Freak improv show accident, 12 dead and 16 injured.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>A murder has happened</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Blame the blood covered jester.</Name>
            <News>Blood covered jester defends himself: "It was just a prank, bro."</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Celebrate it as a offering to the blood god</Name>
            <News>Market closed as the blood god makes an appearence after 10 years.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Put a blanked over the body and tell the surrunding crowd that its under control.</Name>
            <News>People amazed as a body is coverd with a blanket, business as usual.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>No one is at the market</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Steal some sardines to bring to your wife.</Name>
            <News>Citizens confused as something fishy is happening at the manor.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Dive in to the sardine barrel, naked. Nows your chance!</Name>
            <News>top 10 weirdest bucket lists that you must read!</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Go back home.</Name>
            <News>Yearly purge yields no casualties.</News>
            <Doom>0</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>A big muscled warrior wants to fight you</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Throw some leftover sand from you pockets at him and run.</Name>
            <News>Sand related deaths skyrocket, scientist blame global warming.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Take up his challange like a man</Name>
            <News>Man brings gun to a fist fight, it was super effective!</News>
            <Doom>-2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Release your hounds.</Name>
            <News>12 Dead when the market was overrun by hounds.</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>You see a thief stealing from a shop</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Apprehend him and call for the guards.</Name>
            <News>Public execution back in fashion, experts say.</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Realise how easy it is to steal and try to steal some stuff as well.</Name>
            <News>Kidnapping is on an all time high, nobody is safe the experts say.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Ignore the incident.</Name>
            <News>Cursed artifacts gone missing, also a man spontaniously turned himself inside out.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>A wooden crate lies abandoned beside the street. It is inscribed with alien symbols.</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Investigate it closer</Name>
            <News>Worst handwriting in history discovered.</News>
            <Doom>0</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Evacuate the street and call in a specialist</Name>
            <News>Military deployed in the market as man confused upside down crate for a alien artifact.  4 dead.</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Take it home</Name>
            <News>New art installment gone missing! Guards say it was there before lunch.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
    </Questions>
  </House>
  <House>
    <Name>Mayor Estate</Name>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Name>Your wife is angry. For some unknown reason.</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Apologize.</Name>
            <News>Accident at the manor as the mayor falls down the 2nd floor window and stabs himself several times.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Get rid of the cat</Name>
            <News>Crazy cat lady back to her senses, says "wont make that mistake again".</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Try to make sense of her ramblings</Name>
            <News>Terror at the manor! Woman claims husband left the toilet seat up.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>You receive a phone call from an unknown number</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Buy whatever the telemarketer is selling</Name>
            <News>AI controlled tv remotes, a hot new product to have!</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>File a harassment law suit against the caller</Name>
            <News>Girl scouts jailed for suspicion of sexual harassment.</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Throw your phone out of the window</Name>
            <News>Freak accident when a rogue phone kills a man.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>You do some gardening and find a small wishing gnome</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Wish for more wishing gnomes.</Name>
            <News>Man dies as wishing gnome population increases.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Wish for less doom</Name>
            <News>Citizens rejoice as nothing worth mentioning happened today</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Wish for more doom.</Name>
            <News>Citizens confused as nothing happened but they feel more doomed than ever.</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>Your maid did not come to work today.You have to clean the house by yourself.</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Start cleaning the house</Name>
            <News>Lynching continues and no mayor is to be found.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Tell your wife to clean the house.</Name>
            <News>Terror at the manor! Mayor suffers major injuries.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Go look for the maid.</Name>
            <News>Heroic rescue as maid got her hand stuck in jar was saved.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
    </Questions>
  </House>
  <House>
    <Name>Alchemist Tower</Name>
    <Questions>
      <Question>
        <Name>Alchemist offers you a potion to fix your most immediate problems</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Take it! What could possibly go wrong.</Name>
            <News>Deranged man climbs tree claims he is a squirrel</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Dont take it</Name>
            <News>The queen too lazy to get up, announces a public holiday.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Take it but dont use it.</Name>
            <News>Man found eating flower, Other than that no news.</News>
            <Doom>0</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>Alchemist is not at home, but theres a strange bottle at the doorstep</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Open it</Name>
            <News>Freak accident as a man tried opening a bottle and killed 4 people and injured 7.</News>
            <Doom>3</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Give it to the priest</Name>
            <News>Freak accident leaves the church crippled, sunday sabbath cancelled.</News>
            <Doom>-2</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Ignore it and go back to the tavern</Name>
            <News>Drunk man pretends his a pigeon, situation contained.</News>
            <Doom>0</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>The alchemist searches for a missing air elemental</Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Question the alchemists sanity and send him to the asylum for recovery.</Name>
            <News>Village in panic after a derange man claimed the air is missing.</News>
            <Doom>-1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Help alchemist in his search</Name>
            <News>12 dead after a panic over a missing air elemental.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Lie to the alchemist that you saw the elemetalist in the woods.</Name>
            <News>Man says hes not feeling well.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
      <Question>
        <Name>When you go to the alchemist tower, you see him in a trance and drawing spirals on the floor </Name>
        <Answers>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Try to help him.</Name>
            <News>A simple game of twister gone wrong when a man lost the guidebook.</News>
            <Doom>1</Doom>
          </Answer>
          <Answer>
            <Name>Just walk away.</Name>
            <News>Man driven crazy for trying to draw a circle, attacks locals. 4 dead.</News>
            <Doom>2</Doom>
          </Answer>
        </Answers>
        <Trigers />
      </Question>
    </Questions>
  </House>
</ArrayOfHouse>